Guide to the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania Records, 1971-1987 AIS.1987.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Projects, 1971-1987; I.
  - 1095-Providence Health Care Center--Conversion of the Beaver Falls Unit to a 180-Bed LTC Facility, 1981 (Box 177)
  - 1096-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Telephone System, 1981
  - 1097-Beaver Valley Geriatric Center--280 Beds, Side Rails, 380 Overbed Tables and Night Stands, 1981
  - 1098-Brownsville General Hospital--Renovations-JCAH and Life Safety Code Renovations, 1981
  - 1099-Monsour Medical Center--Replace Two Fluoroscopic/Radiographic Units, 1981
  - 1100-Hospice of Greene County--Primary Health Care, 1981
  - 1101-St. Francis General Hospital--Developmental Evaluative Services for Children, 1981
  - 1102-Mon Valley United Health Services--Comprehensive Health Services Program, 1981
  - 1103-Valley Special Needs Program--ARC Child Development Program, 1981
  - 1104-Rehabilitation Institute of Pittsburgh--ARC Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1105-St. Francis General Hospital--Installation of Centrifugal Chiller and Automatic Temperature Control Valve, 1981
  - 1106-Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--Consultation and Education Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1107-St. Francis General Hospital--Consultation and Education Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1108-Human Services Center--Initial Operation Renewal Grant Application, 1981 (Box 178)
  - 1109-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--RHI Funds, 1981
  - 1110-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Computerized Electrocardiographic Analysis System, 1981
  - 1111-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Cardiac Monitoring System, 1981
  - 1112-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Renovation of the Heating, Ventilating and Air Conditioning System, 1981
  - 1113-Community College of Allegheny County--Licensed Practical Nursing Program at South Campus, 1981
  - 1114-Jeannette District Memorial Hospital--Renovation of Ancillary Services, 1981
  - 1115-Sewickley Valley Hospital--CT Whole Body Scanner, 1981
  - 1116-Lemington Home for the Aged--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1117-Dialysis Clinics--10 Stations in New Kensington, 1981
  - 1118-Suburban General Hospital--Acquisition of a CT Scanner, 1981 (Box 179)
  - 1119-Alma Illery Medical Center--Primary Care Health Services, 1981
  - 1120-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1121-National Medical Care-Bio-Medical Applications of Butler--Expansion of Facility from 7 to 10 Stations, 1981
  - 1122-Alan A. Axelson, M.D.--Construction of a Private Psychiatric Hospital, 1981
  - 1123-Eye and Ear Hospital--Surface Parking Lot, 1981
  - 1124-Ohio Valley General Hospital--Acquisition of a Full Body CT Scanner, 1981
  - 1125-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Acquisition of Replacement Telephone Equipment, 1981 (Box 180)
  - 1126-South Hills Health System--Consultation and Education Services Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1127-Valley View Nursing Home--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1128-Aliquippa Hospital--Acquisition of a CT Scanner, 1981
  - 1129-Centerville Clinics--Optometric Equipment Grant Application, 1981
  - 1130-Centerville Clinics--R.H.I. Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1131-Magee-Womens Hospital--Energy Conservation Project, 1981
  - 1132-not present
  - 1133-West Haven Nursing Home--83 Bed Expansion, 1981
  - 1134-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1981 (Box 181)
  - 1135-Torrance State Hospital--Power Plant Alterations, 1981
  - 1136-Butler County Commissioners' Council on Drugs and Alcohol--Tertiary Program for Female Alcoholics, 1981
  - 1137-Step-by-Step--Development of 32 ICF/MR Beds, 1981
  - 1138-Beverly Enterprises--Construction of 120-Bed Nursing Home, 1981
  - 1139-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Lothrop/Darragh Parking Garage, 1981
  - 1140-Turtle Creek Valley Mental Health/Mental Retardation--Consultation and Education Services, 1981
  - 1141-Allegheny County Health Department--Rodent Control/Neighborhood Improvement Continuation Program, 1981 (Box 182)
  - 1142-Dialysis Clinics--Expansion from 8 to 12 Stations, 1982
  - 1143-Allegheny General Hospital--Addition of 6 Dialysis Stations, 1982
  - 1144-Forbes Health System--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1145-University of Pittsburgh School of Nursing--Adult Primary Health Care Nursing Grant, 1981
  - 1146-Allegheny Valley School--Renovate and Convert 70-Bed PLF to a 57-Bed ICF/MR, 1981
  - 1147-Allegheny County Health Department--Comprehensive Immunization Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1148-South Hills Health System--Medical Office Building Acquisition, 1981
  - 1149-Medical Center of Beaver County--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1150-Greensburg Nursing and Convalescent Center--120-Bed Long Term Care Facility, 1981 (Box 183)
  - 1151-Indiana County Head Start--Child Health Initiative for Lifelong Development, 1981
  - 1152-Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District--Human Resources Development Program Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1153-American Health Systems--Addition of 39-Beds at Oakmont Nursing Center, 1981
  - 1154-Unity Pavilion--110-Bed Nursing Home Facility, 1981
  - 1155-West Penn Hospital--Cost Increase, 1981 (Box 184)
  - 1156-Almar Radiologists--Replacement of Whole Body CT Scanner, 1981
  - 1157-Monroeville Manor Associates--240-Bed Nursing Home, 1981
  - 1158-Shadyside Hospital--Purchase, Install and Operate A Vascular Procedure Room, 1981
  - 1159-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Conversion of Dormitory Space for Physician Offices and Dialysis Unit, 1981
  - 1160-Dr. Alan A. Axelson--Construction of a Psychiatric Hospital for Children and Adolescents, 1981
  - 1161-Turtle Creek Valley Mental Health/Mental Retardation--Preventive Support Systems for At-Risk Population, 1981
  - 1162-Harmarville Rehabilitation Center--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1163-Montefiore Hospital--Replace Telephone System, 1981
  - 1164-Almar Illery Medical Center--Supplemental Manpower Application Requesting National Health Service Corps Professionals for the St. Clair Village Health Center, 1982
  - 1165-Mid Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative, 1982
  - 1166-Sto-Rox Neighborhood Family Health Center--Urban Health Initiative, 1982
  - 1167-Braddock General Hospital--Acquisition of a Whole Body CT Scanner, 1982 (Box 185)
  - 1168-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1169-The North Fayette County Municipal Authority--Grant Application for Water Fluoridation Project, 1982
  - 1170-Life Management Consultants--Development of Six Sites, 1982
  - 1171-Rehab Hospital Services Corporation--Construction of 85-Bed Comprehensive Physical Rehabilitation Center, 1982 (Box 185-186)
  - 1172-Living Care Services Corporation-Friendship Village--60-Bed LTC Facility, 1982 (Box 187)
  - 1173-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Acquisition of a Whole-Body CT Scanner, 1982
  - 1174-South Side Hospital--Establish Occupational Therapy Service, 1982
  - 1175-West Penn Hospital--Expansion of Cardiac Catheterization Suite, 1982
  - 1176-Braddock General Hospital--Replacement of Telephone System, 1982
  - 1177-Leader Nursing Centers--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1178-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Continuation Grant, 1982
  - 1179-Miners Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1982
  - 1180-Pennsylvania Regional Planning and Development Commission--Shannock Valley Medical Facility RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1181-Mobile Imaging--Shared CT Scanning Services, 1982 (Box 188)
  - 1182-Susquehanna American Associates--120-Bed LTC Facility, 1982
  - 1183-Susquehanna American Associates--Construction of a 120-Bed Nursing Home-Baldock Health Care Center, 1982
  - 1184-Mercy Hospital--Replacement of Radiology Equipment, 1982
  - 1185-Keystone Company--120-Bed Nursing Home-Meadowlands Health Care Center, 1982
  - 1186-Keystone Company--120-Bed Nursing Home-West Hills Health Care Center, 1982 (Box 189)
  - 1187-Southern Hills Nursing Center--120-Bed Long Term Care Facility, 1982
  - 1188-Marian Manor--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1189-Forbes Health System--CT Scanning Services at Columbia Health Center, 1982
  - 1190-Cumberland Associates--120-Bed Nursing Home in Franklin Township, 1982
  - 1191-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Ambulatory Care Center and CT Scanner, 1982
  - 1192-Allegheny County Health Department--Tuberculosis Control, 1982
  - 1193-Greensburg North Associates--120-Bed Nursing Home, 1982
  - 1194-South Side Hospital--Acquisition of a Whole Body CT Scanner, 1982 (Box 190)
  - 1195-Alle-Kiski Valley Health Plan--Federal Qualification for the Development of an HMO, 1982
  - 1196-Lancer Development Corporation--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1197-University of Pittsburgh--Renovation and Expansion of Falk Clinic, 1982
  - 1198-Citizens General Hospital--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1199-St. Francis General Hospital--Replacement of Inpatient Psychiatric Facilities, 1982 (Box 190-191)
  - 1200-The Verland Foundation--Cost Increase, 1982 (Box 191)
  - 1201-Suburban General Hospital--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1202-Pittsburgh Public Schools--Adolescent Pregnancy Demonstration Project, 1982
  - 1203-Southeastern Greene Community Health Center--Adolescent Family Life Demonstration Project, 1982
  - 1204-The Children's Home of Pittsburgh--Adolescent Pregnancy Program, 1982
  - 1205-Try-Again Homes--Adolescent Family Life Demonstration Program, 1982
  - 1206-YWCA of Washington--Adolescent Pregnancy Program, 1982
  - 1207-Theiss Health Center--Adolescent Pregnancy Program, 1982
  - 1208-University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine--Adolescent Life Demonstration Project, 1982
  - 1209-Georgian Terrace Associates--120-Bed Nursing Home, 1982
  - 1210-Forbes Health System--Expansion of Inpatient Psychiatric Services, 1982
  - 1211-Medical Center of Beaver County--Addition of 2 Beds, 1982
  - 1212-Shadyside Hospital--Addition of 9 Critical Care Beds with a Reduction of 9 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1982
  - 1213-Oakmont Nursing Center Associates-American Health Systems--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1214-Mayview State Hospital--Handicapped Standards Improvement, 1982 (Box 192)
  - 1215-H.C. Frick Community Hospital--Acquisition of a Whole Body CT-Scanner, 1982
  - 1216-Mayview State Hospital--Installation of Fluidized Bed Boiler, 1983
  - 1217-Mayview State Hospital--Partitions for Patients Building, 1983
  - 1218-Mayview State Hospital--Installation of Air-Conditioning at Forrester Building, 1983
  - 1219-Greene County Memorial Hospital--Expansion of Facility, 1983
  - 1220-May's Manor--Development of a 40-Bed Intermediate Care Nursing Home, 1983
  - 1221-Green County Memorial Hospital--Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention and Services, 1983
  - 1222-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1223-Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--Addition of 3 Beds, 1982
  - 1224-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Addition of 10-Beds, 1982
  - 1225-St. Francis General Hospital--Purchase of Land, 1982
  - 1226-The Verland Foundation--Addition of 7 ICF/MR Beds, 1982
  - 1227-DeFluri Enterprises--Construction of a 180-Bed Nursing Home in Westmoreland County, 1982
  - 1228-Westmoreland Hospital--Addition of 10 Beds, 1982
  - 1229-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Modernization and Expansion, 1982 (Box 193)
  - 1230-Presbyterian Association on Aging--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1231-Magee-Womens Hospital--Cost Increase, 1982
  - 1232-Alma Illery Medical Center--Health Service Development Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1233-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Immunization Project Grant Application, 1982
  - 1234-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Courtyard Cost Increase, 1982 (Box 194)
  - 1235-Presbyterian University Hospital--Expansion of ERSD Capacity by 12 Stations, 1982
  - 1236-Allegheny County Health Department--Immunization Program Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1237-Uniontown Hospital--Acquisition of a Whole-Body CT Scanner, 1982
  - 1238-Allegheny General Hospital--Establishment of a Discrete 16-Bed Psychiatric Unit, 1982
  - 1239-Divine Providence Hospital--Renovation/Expansion, 1982 (Box 195)
  - 1240-Allegheny County Health Department--Rodent Control/Neighborhood Improvement Program Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1241-Presbyterian-University Hospital--ICU Expansion, 1982
  - 1242-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Develop a Radiation/Medical Oncology Facility, 1983
  - 1243-The Verland Foundation--Addition of 13 ICF/MR Beds, 1982
  - 1244-Centerville Clinics--RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1982
  - 1245-Riverside Terrace Nursing Center--Construction of a 120-Bed Nursing Home, 1983 (Box 196)
  - 1246-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--11th Floor Renovation, 1982
  - 1247-The Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Cost Increase and Change in Scope on Project, 1983
  - 1248-Shadyside Hospital--Replacement of Angiography Equipment with Digital Subtraction Angiography, 1982
  - 1249-Braddock General Hospital--Addition of 10 Psychiatric Beds, 1982
  - 1250-Waynesburg College--Baccalaureate Program in Nursing Feasibility Study, 1983
  - 1251-Lawrence L. Gibson, M.D.--Establish a Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgical Care Center, 1983
  - 1252-Presbyterian Association on Aging--2nd Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1253-Bio-Medical Applications of Greensburg--Expansion of Facility from 10 to 12 Stations, 1983
  - 1254-Mobile Imaging--Shared CT Scanner Services, 1983 (Box 197)
  - 1255-Presbyterian University Hospital--Refinancing of Hospital Bond Issue, 1983
  - 1256-Greensburg Nursing and Convalescent Center--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1257-Indiana Hospital--Acquisition of a Full-Body CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1258-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1259-The Washington Hospital--Air Conditioning-Phase I, 1983
  - 1260-Sto-Rox Family Health Center--Urban Health Initiative, 1983
  - 1261-NE/Butler Community Medical Center--Rural Health Initiative, 1983
  - 1262-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--UHCP Family House, 1983
  - 1263-Dialysis Clinics--Establish a 10-Station Facility in Upper St. Clair, 1983 (Box 198)
  - 1264-St. Francis Hospital of New Castle--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1265-Allegheny General Hospital--Replacement of Head Scanner with a Full Body CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1266-Miners Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1983
  - 1267-The Washington Hospital--Ambulatory Surgery Expansion, 1983
  - 1268-University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine--National Health Service Corp, 1983
  - 1269-Allegheny County Health Department--Tuberculosis Control Project, 1983
  - 1270-Champ Development Corporation-Rochester Manor--120-Bed LTC Facility, 1983
  - 1271-Providence Health Center--Cost Increase and Change in Scope on Project, 1983
  - 1272-The Children's Home of Pittsburgh--Transitional Infant Care, 1983
  - 1273-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--North Wing Elevator Project, 1983 (Box 199)
  - 1274-Divine Providence Hospital--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1275-Citizens General Hospital--Refinancing of Existing Debt, 1983
  - 1276-The United Methodist Home--Nursing Unit Renovation and Addition, 1983
  - 1277-The McMurray Hills Manor--Addition of 10 LTC Beds and 19 Residential Beds, 1983
  - 1278-Bio-Medicial Applications-BMA of South Hills--10 Stations, 1983
  - 1279-Aliquippa Hospital--Construction of a Laundry Facility, 1983
  - 1280-Community Dialysis Centers--10-Station Hemodialysis Facility in the South Hills, 1983
  - 1281-Develpments Incorporated--Construction of a Physicians Office on the Campus of Mercy Hospital, 1983
  - 1282-Alma Illery Medical Center--Establish a Satellite Clinic in Rankin, 1983
  - 1283-X-U-N Diagnostic Associates--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1284-Shared Mobile--CT Scanning Services with Ohio Valley and Aliquippa Hospitals, 1983
  - 1285-Western Center--Handicapped Standards, 1983 (Box 200)
  - 1286-Children's Hospital--8 Medical/Surgical Pediatric Beds Converted to Respiratory Beds, 1983
  - 1287-McKeesport Hospital--Urban Health Initiative, 1983
  - 1288-West End Health Center--Community Health Center Grant Application, 1983
  - 1289-Allegheny Health Education and Research--Acquisition of Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, 1983
  - 1290-Uinversity of Pittsburgh--Prevention of Black Infant Deaths in Pittsburgh Grant Application, 1983
  - 1291-Riverside Nursing Centers--120-Bed LTC Facility, 1983
  - 1292-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1293-Magee-Womens Hospital--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1294-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--R.H.I. Continuation Grant, 1983
  - 1295-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Addition of 10 Beds, 1983
  - 1296-University Health Center--Develop NMR Facility, 1983 (Box 201)
  - 1297-Centerville Clinics --Home Health Services Expansion Grant Applications, 1983
  - 1298-Crane Associates--Construction of a 76-Bed LTC Facility -Harmon House Convalescent Center, 1984
  - 1299-Timber Ridge--Construction of a 120-Bed LTC Facility, 1983
  - 1300-Allegheny County Health Department--V.D. Research and Demonstration Grant Application, 1983
  - 1301-Central Medical Center and Hospital--Acquisition of a Full-Body CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1302-Primary Care Health Services--Community Health Services Continuation Grant, 1983
  - 1303-Mercy Hospital--Installation of Automated Laboratory Information System, 1983
  - 1304-Mercy Hospital of Pittsburgh--Computerized Hospital Information System, 1984
  - 1305-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--Geriatric Psychiatry/Behavioral Neurology Expansion Project, 1983 (Box 202)
  - 1306-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Ambulatory Care Center, 1983
  - 1307-Canonsburg General Hospital--Addition of 10-Beds, 1983
  - 1308-Central Medical Center and Hospital--Renovations/Reduction of Beds by 18, 1983
  - 1309-Westmoreland Hospital--Refinancing of Current Bond Issue, 1983
  - 1310-Allegheny County Health Department--Immunization Continuation Grant, 1983
  - 1311-Beverly Enterprises--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1312-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Addition of 10-Beds, 1983
  - 1313-Hillcrest Children's Center--Adolescent Pregnancy Program Grant Application, 1983
  - 1314-Community Dialysis Services of McKeesport--Expansion from 7 to 12 Dialysis Stations, 1983
  - 1315-West Penn Hospital--Re-designation of Beds, 1983
  - 1316-Southeastern Greene Community Health Center--Community Health Center Continuation Grant Application, 1983
  - 1317-Divine Providence Hospital--Advance Refunding of Existing Long Term Indebtedness, 1983
  - 1318-Continental Care Corporation/Jack Rees Rehabilitation Services--Addition of 8 Beds/Improvements, 1983
  - 1319-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1983
  - 1320-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--Cost Increase, 1983 (Box 203)
  - 1321-C.A.T. Scan Association--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1983
  - 1322-Indiana Hospital--Cost Increase, 1983
  - 1323-Oakleaf Health Center Association--Construction of a 117-Bed Nursing Home, 1983
  - 1324-Bio-Medical Applications of Southwestern Pennsylvania--Addition of 1 Dialysis Station, 1983
  - 1325-Continental Care Corporation--Addition of 10 Beds/Improvements, 1983
  - 1326-Dialysis Clinics--Establish an 8-Station Dialysis Facility in the McKeesport Area, 1983
  - 1327-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Immunization Continuation Grant Application, 1983
  - 1328-The Podiatry Hospital of Pittsburgh--Replacement of non-Conforming Beds and Compliance with the Life Safety Code, 1983
  - 1329-Allegheny Health, Education and Research--Refunding of Outstanding Bonds, 1983 (Box 204)
  - 1330-Graziano Development--159-Bed LTC Facility in Squirrel Hill, 1983
  - 1331-St. Francis Hospital of New Castle--Addition of 10 Psychiatric Beds, 1983
  - 1332-The Ellwood City Hospital--Cost Increase, 1984
  - 1333-Susquehanna American Associates--Cost Increase on Humbert Lane Health Care Center, 1983
  - 1334-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--Addition of 10 Beds, 1983
  - 1335-The Washington Hospital--Special Procedures Room, 1984
  - 1336-Center for Emergency Medicine of Western Pennsylvania--Multi-Institutional Community Based System for Patient Transportation, 1984
  - 1337-South Hills Health System--Replacement of Telephone System, 1984
  - 1338-The Mercy Hospital of Pittsburgh--Change in Method of Financing on the Hospital Information System Project, 1983
  - 1339-Latrobe Area Hospital--Decrease of Long Term Care Beds by 18, 1983
  - 1340-Southwestern Health Center--Ambulatory Surgical Center, 1984 (Box 205)
  - 1341-Manor Health Care Corporation--Construction of a 120-Bed LTC Facility in Scott Township, 1984
  - 1342-Jefferson Hills Manor--Nursing Home Expansion, 1984
  - 1343-Manor Health Care Corporation--120-Bed Nursing Home in Bethel Park, 1984
  - 1344-Allegheny Valley School--Expansion of Pittsburgh Campus by 6 ICF/MR Beds, 1984
  - 1345-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Digital Subtraction Angiography Equipment, 1985
  - 1346-Mobile Imaging--Shared Mobile CT Scanner between Clarion Osteopathic, Ellwood City, United Community Hospital and St. Francis Hospital of New Castle, 1984
  - 1347-The United Methodist Home--Construction and Renovation, 1984 (Box 206)
  - 1348-The South Side Hospital-Support Service Facility--Demolition and Parking, 1984
  - 1349-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Labor, Post-Partum and Nursery Facilities, 1984
  - 1350-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1351-F.O.R. Neighborhood Corporation--Urban Health Initiative, 1984
  - 1352-NE/Butler County Community Medical Center--Rural Health Initiative, 1984
  - 1353-Dr. Frank J. Suatoni--Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgical Center, 1984
  - 1354-Miners Clinics--R.H.I. Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1355-Baptist Homes of Western Pennsylvania--Construction and Renovation to Replace Intermediate Care Facilities, 1984
  - 1356-Shadyside Hospital--Replace CT Scanner and Renovation of CT Procedure Room, 1984 (Box 207)
  - 1357-Shadyside Hospital--Parking Garage Addition, 1984
  - 1358-Presbyterian Medical Center of Oakmont--Replacement and Expansion, 1984
  - 1359-Continental Care Corporation-Kade Nursing Home--Addition of 5 Beds, 1984
  - 1360-Continental Care Corporation-Briarcliff Pavilion--Addition of 10 Beds, 1984
  - 1361-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Replacement of 20 MeV Linear Accelerators, 1984
  - 1362-Jefferson Hills Manor--Expansion, 1984
  - 1363-Dialysis Clinics--Addition of 1 Dialysis Station, 1984
  - 1364-Dialysis Clinics-Aliquippa Facility--Expansion from 10 to 12 Stations, 1984
  - 1365-Central Medical Center and Hospital--Reduction of Beds by 18, 1984
  - 1366-Frank V. Maida, M.D.--Ambulatory Surgical Facility in Westmoreland County, 1984
  - 1367-Indian Creek Nursing Center--Addition of 10 Beds, 1984
  - 1368-Primary Care Health Services--Rankin Family Health Facility Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1369-Magnetic Imaging Associates--NMR Facility, 1985 (Box 208)
  - 1370-Surgicenter Associates--Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgical Facility in Westmoreland County, 1984
  - 1371-Montefiore Hospital--Replace CT Scanner, 1984
  - 1372-Westmoreland Human Opportunities--Expansion of Homemaker/Home Health Aide Services, 1984
  - 1373-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--R.H.I. Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1374-Surgery Centers Corporation--Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgery Facility in Pittsburgh, 1984
  - 1375-The Rehabilitation Institute of Pittsburgh--Personal Care Attendant Training Program, 1984
  - 1376-St. Francis General Hospital--Purchase Existing CT Scanner from Almar Radiologists, 1984
  - 1377-Westmoreland Hospital--Purchase of Digital Subtraction Angiography Equipment, 1984
  - 1378-Latrobe Area Hospital--Homemaker Program Grant Application, 1984
  - 1379-Latrobe Area Hospital--Family Caregiver Project, 1984